goviral.com 2015-03-15

# Be On - Privacy and Cookies

## Privacy Policy

References in this Privacy Policy to "we" or "us" refers to goviral (trading as "Be On") and its group companies, including without limitation, AOL Inc. and its direct and indirect subsidiaries. References to "content" includes advertising. You agree that we may transfer your personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy to our group companies worldwide.

When you visit our sites ("Our Websites"), sites within Be On for Publishers ("Network Websites"), or view a video distributed within the Be On player, we collect a variety of information about you and put it to different uses. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect and how we use it. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected through third parties in which we do not have any control. The use of data collected by such third parties will be subject to that third party's own Privacy Policy.

### Visitor Information

When you visit Our Websites, Network Websites, or view a video distributed within the Be On player, we may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to anonymously track how you use our website and our player. To find out more about how Be On may use cookies please see our Cookie Policy.

For more information on cookies in general, please visit the [IAB Cookies page](http://www.iabeurope.eu/cookies-faq.aspx).

If you have disabled the Be On cookies or the cookies on your browser you may not be able to receive the full benefit of Our Websites or the Network Websites.

### Data Collection

Certain parts of Our Websites require that you register and provide us with your email address and other information. We will use this data to provide you with our services and to inform you (by email) about any future services that we may offer. If you wish us to remove your email address from our systems, just send an email to [beon-legal@teamaol.com](mailto:beon-legal@teamaol.com) setting out your request. Other data that we may collect from you may include:

  * (if you sign up as a Be On publisher or Be On advertiser) Registration information such as your name, email address, payment details, and telephone number;
  * Other information you provide to us, for example when you ask us to email certain content to a third party or when you ask us to post such content on a third party site; 
  * Information you have provided when you entered a competition;
  * Your correspondence with us;
  * Your responses to market research and surveys;
  * Feedback that you provide to us;
  * Technical and diagnotistic information, such as browser type, operating system, how you connect to the internet, your internet protocol (IP) address. 

The information that we collect about you may be supplemented with information which is obtained from other companies that we may use to better understand you as a customer and to provide you with better, more relevant content and advertising. This data may in some cases be personally identifiable data.

### How we may use Data

We, or third parties acting under our control, may use data that personally identifies you in order to:

  * Operate and improve our services;
  * To enhance your experience when using Our Websites and Network Websites, and our video player by personalizing or targeting the content, advertising and promotions made available to you;
  * Communicate with you by electronic methods, including email, SMS, text, video and picture, about our offers, products and services and well as those provided by third parties;
  * Conduct research and analyisis;
  * Contact you regarding technical problems you may be incurring;
  * Provide you with service messages;
  * Contact you for marketing purposes or for any communications with you;
  * Transfer information about you if we purchase or sell a business unit, take over another company(ies) (or is taken over), or vary out corporate reorganization. The data that personally identifies you may be disclosed or transferred along with other business assets, to actual or potential purchasers. However, your personal data will be protected through appropriate confidentiality obligations.

### Data Preferences

If you wish to change how Be On uses cookie data, you can do so by changing your internet browser settings and your flash player settings.

To change how your browser uses cookies from our domains please go to your browser's cookie settings to reject all cookies, accept only certain cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Please note that you will need to renew these settings if you delete your cookies after these preferences are made. These settings may also not apply if you are using a different computer or internet browser. The domains specific to Be On are: beon.aolnetworks.com, eisenstien.dk, video-loader.com and videos.aolnetworks.com.

To change how your flash video player uses flash cookies from Be On [please go here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html) and follow the on screen instructions for changing your flash player cookie settings.

If you opt out of these technologies, you will continue to see advertising displayed on the site and our video player, however, the advertising may not be targeted to you.

### Sharing Data with Third Parties

Except as we explain in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose any information that personally identifies you to third parties unless you have consented to us doing so, except in the following circumstances:

  * To provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of us and have confidentiality agreements in place;
  * If we are required to disclose the information pursuant to a subpoena, court order, legal process, or to any legitimate request by the authorities;
  * We believe it is necessary to share this information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities.

We may also use and sell the information we collect on you by putting it together with other information we collect on other users in such a manner that does not identify you. We do not sell nor rent any information that we have that identifies you personally.

### Storage of Your Data

We are a global organization and many of the computers and companies that process information about you by us or on our behalf are based outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). This means that the data that relates to youmay be transferred to, processed and held both inside and outside the EEA. Countries outside of the EEA may not have similar data protection laws to the EEA. However, if we transfer your information outside the EEA in this way, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected in compliance with applicable data protection laws and this Privacy Policy. In the event that we transfer any data to AOL Inc. (our ultimate parent company), your data will be protected as AOL Inc. and its affiliates, adhere to the EU-US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement, and is registered with the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe harbor Program. [Click here for more information](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

### Children under 13

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If we learn that we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database.

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees or our partners who we believe reasonably need to have access to that information to provide services to you or to do their jobs. We have technical, physical and administrative procedures to help protect information about you from loss, misuse and alteration. However, no data transmission or storage can be 100% secure, and we cannot warrant the security of any such information.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. Typically we will only do so if: we have got something wrong and need to correct it; the law has changed and we need to react to the change; we have changed our service and the changes need to be reflected in this Privacy Policy. Such changes will be reflected in this Privacy Policy and we will update the Published Date which will be the date in which the changes take effect.

## Cookie Policy

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers downloaded on to your computer when you access certain websites, including those within Be On for Publishers. Cookies allow a website to recognise a user’s preferences as previously chosen by the user when they return to a site. A cookie itself does not contain or collect information. However, when it is read by a server in conjunction with a web browser it can help a website deliver a more user-friendly service. For example, remembering account details or previous purchases.

Cookies are filed in the memory of your browser and each one typically contains:

  * The name of the server the cookie was sent from
  * The lifetime of the cookie
  * A value – usually a randomly generated unique number
  * Other data a site may have about your browsing that is stored for future use and allows the site to remember your browser.

### Cookies are Secure

The website server which sends the cookie uses the unique number to recognise you when you return to a site or browse from page to page. Only the server that sent a cookie can read, and therefore use, that cookie. Cookies are central to the customisation of the internet and online behavioural advertising usually works using cookies.

### Session and Persistent

There are two types of cookies – session and persistent. Session cookies only exist during a user’s online session and they disappear from the user’s computer when the user closes his/her browser. Persistent cookies stay on your computer after the browser has been closed.

### Web Beacons

Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on web pages that can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit that web page, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing that page. Many websites, including Be On may also use Flash cookies that operate similarly to browser cookies.

When you visit the Be On for Publishers websites or view a video distributed within the Be On player, we use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to anonymously track how you use them. Examples of data collected include your IP address, internet browser, operating system, sites you visit, the video that you watch in the Be On player and similar. We may also collect information about how you interact with our website and the Be On player, including what you click on and the content you view to help remember your preferences, measure and research the effectiveness of the Be On service and to customise the content provided via the Be On player.

We may also make use of the Google Analytics service which also tracks your use of our website via anonymous cookies and other means. Data captured or stored using cookies uniquely identifies you to us but does not (on its own) tell us your name or anything else about who you are. We use this information for the following general purposes: to build up an opinion about what kind of content you want to see so that we can filter out things that we think you will not be interested in, in an aggregated form with other data from other users to give us useful information about visitors to our site and users of our player.

### Be On Cookies

Below is a list of cookies that Be On may store on your computer to provide the services set out above. The list contains all possible cookies that we may set on Be On for Publishers and the Be On player. Unless you use all of our products and services, you are unlikely to have all of these cookies on your computer.

Cookie and Domain | Party | Content | Expiry  
---|---|---|---  
**PHPSESSID**  
videos.aolnetworks.com | 1st | Hashed unique session id | Session  
**NSC_wjq_mpoxfc_80**  
videos.aolnetworks.com | 1st | Unique session ID | Session  
**_utma**  
videos.aolnetworks.com | 1st | Google Analytics data | 2 years  
**_utmb**  
videos.aolnetworks.com | 1st | Google Analytics data | Session  
**_utmc**  
videos.aolnetworks.com | 1st | Google Analytics data | Session  
**_utmz**  
videos.aolnetworks.com | 1st | Google Analytics data | 6 months  
**countryID**  
s.srvntrk.com | 3rd | Country of user for delivery of correct content | 1 month  
**cw_**  
s.srvntrk.com | 3rd | CW id | 1 month  
**NSC_wjq_mpoxfc_wjefpmpbefs_80**  
videos.goviral-content.com | 3rd | Unique Session ID | Session  
**NSC_wjq_mpoxfc_wjefpmpbefs_80**  
player.goviral-content.com | 3rd | Unique Session ID | Session  
**NSC_wjq_mpoxfc_wjefpmpbefs_80**  
player.video-loader.com | 3rd | Unique Session ID | Session  
**NSC_wjq_mpoxfc_wjefpmpbefs_80**  
videos.video-loader.com | 3rd | Unique Session ID | Session  
**NSC_wjq_mpoxfc_wjefpmpbefs_80**  
files.video-loader.com | 3rd | Unique Session ID | Session  
  
### Third Party Cookies

The following third party advertising networks and service providers may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in connection with advertisements and services offered through Be On for Publishers and the Be On player. The information stored on a third party’s cookie about your use of the website and/or the Be On player (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored on servers outside of the EU.

The use of cookies, web beacons or similar technologies by third parties is subject to their own privacy policies.

### Opting Out

To opt out of using cookies on this website, please click the button below.

### Contact Us

You may contact the data controller, Nick Roveta, via email at [**beon-legal@teamaol.com**](mailto:beon-legal@teamaol.com).

_goviral Limited trading as Be On. Last Published 30th April 2013._
